hey guys this is a very quick video to
let you know a couple of really
interesting things that are coming up
we've got an interview with Ken Wilber
the integral philosopher coming up next
week which we're really excited about
and also a live event and an interview
within McGilchrist the author of the
master in his emissary so the reason for
this is to ask for some questions from
the community before we do both of these
interviews and we're going to give
priority to patrons but if you've got a
question for either of them put it below
in the comments to this and yeah Ally's
gonna talk a little bit more about the
live event we've got coming up next week
yeah so as well as recording an
interview with Ian McGilchrist we're
also gonna have a live event part of our
new series rebel wisdom live so we're
going to be hopefully live-streaming it
I also wanted to take the opportunity to
say thank you to everyone who stuck with
us in our experimental first run with
the war on art which was an event with
Tim Loughton Lionel Shriver which we'll
also be putting up soon we're just
working on some sound issues that some
of the people who were watching the live
stream might have noticed so the event
happening next Tuesday is with Ian
McGilchrist it's called divided brain
divided world it's at 7 o'clock at 91
which is in Brick Lane in London so if
you're in London come along it's only
about 10 tickets left so I would book
fairly soon if you're interested and
again we're gonna be hopefully
live-streaming it
so if seven o'clock GMT you can google
that whatever it is in your local
timezone will will hopefully be live as
well so you can watch it and in addition
to the live event we've also got an
interview with a McGilchrist that we're
going to do next Tuesday and just to
kind of recap who in McGilchrist is and
he wrote a book called the master in his
emissary he did a very well-received
interview with Jordan Peterson and I
think February this year and the main
theory of the master Owens emissary is
that there are the the different
hemispheres of the brain have different
functions left hemisphere much more
analytical much more mechanical much
more atomistic and the right brain being
much more holistic and not a lot of the
different ways that we perceive the
world and the conflict between the
different ways we perceive the world can
be
seen as a conflict between the right
brain and the left brain so we're really
interested to crowdsource questions for
ear McGilchrist we so put some questions
in the comments below below this video
and as always we're gonna priority to
patrons but if you ask a good question
there's every chance that we're gonna
ask it to him and as well as a
McGilchrist next week about two days
later we're flying to Boulder Colorado
to interview Ken Wilber which we're both
really excited about being fans of his
integral philosophy and we know there's
lots of fans on the channel as well so
if you have questions for Ken Wilber
that you would like us to ask we
obviously can't guarantee every question
will go in put your questions in the
comments and you can also ask them
through patreon and with both Emma
Gilchrist and Ken Wilber we'll be doing
some patreon only specials and exclusive
content as well so thank you for
watching see you soon